Santin, without stats,
I'm teaching this step along the way,
probably Sabatini, and our plan is
about 15 years. I'm on all the results
for Gusev, Gusev, all 15 views.
We finished 8 years ago. Pebble
Berlin came to be king,
and many people didn't show up from the very
beginning. So, I'm reviewing previous
years every day. I'll do some
spreads to defend myself, and
Newcomen is disgusting. So, you have the leaflets
when you entered. I brought this out to
help you make this review. So,
in the evening, I'll review the most
old Gilada classes for 3 types
on the first page. Dog n.d.
Well, the side
sat down and we start on the next
page there the car salesman is always to
you, Kapa
sells a car, a couple of the way I
like to review the material from the previous
pictures
I like to do it with pictures the pictures are
easy to fill out
I name and coat of arms have an idea and match the idea of ​​the
picture and yawn it's easier to remember and
also new material we have a picture
with artists
you can test your
own close the letters and look
at the picture and try to remember the
meaning so today I well yes to torment you with
the meanings of the first 6 pictures and from classes
from the class of previous years starting from
tomorrow day of
exams we will have an exam and plans
I will take one name
from the list of students and I will give you a
microphone and you will have a chance to embarrass yourself
Mexico
like in front of five hundred people good
those you won't need to win choose a name
if you want you can pull out the curtain with your own
gonna be done
give Tim and 100 dollars to the Stillavins
for the name those
fifty-fifty you are a
real business so number 1 pictures
[music]
we have already done 108th became 12
I started this review  Last year, so
if you want the first 108 types of
online TV file,
we can give you the file online. You can
get the first 108 and dims and such a
normal official now sleep site
on the site overnight without it's free
online and so I start the stages of these guys
teapot
dripping in the picture of the guy who sells the
car in English, we call it a
paper seller, this city, a bad
word you about buying this car. The
last owner was 80 years old,
Fiona Joyteka Winter, and she drove the
car only once to see in church,
a'most fire, this car is practically
new,
and they will talk a lot and you will buy the
car next week, Samantha,
as we call them, the seller was
any car, Beckman, they have very well-
delivered speech, you will buy fewer cars and
least of all with a brush, we speak
English, good work after
you communicate with them, do you really
want to buy in the paws to drown the air, why am
I here with this picture, we love in this lam
rim tradition steps of the steps on the
way and became for unlucky one
thousand two hundred thousand jing in one book,
we save in different catalogs already
catalog  320,000
[music]
Mongolia barbecue Russians fields we
found books and now we have 5 generations of them, it will take us
just to enter all these books
collected in 1 click
we break this down what you are now for you Rome
means the first thing is this second this 3 this
4 this house here the needle no need to
think about just take one step step step step
and exit teclast here
if you start a class here just
come each kulik style
next year the bank more
soup-puree background very Russia to
Ivan etc.  I was there this year,
Sting's mother, Parfinsky, my friend from
Singapore kidnapped me, antiban, and we
went to Bali. We had a
group, I said more,
agreed, and the whole year we're going
to the bank game, agreed, everything is there, you are
slaves, enlightenment, whether Pan and the enlightened,
and 8,
and for that, I'm here, we are baseball,
and this book is about that, I do one, two, three, four, five, six,
finish ten, fog, no need to
think much, ollin, ollin, panel, they
just press and
Thailand, more pain, pain, pain, pain, bureau,
then, but understand, half the window of the figure,
come on, this is very close to enlightenment,
David Coleman, just step by step in the
beginning, we'll break it off for you, Rome,
this Rome car salesman,
he will do what I'm doing now,
you have such beautiful children, one, two,
three, and you can become enlightened from a
little spirit, well, this is traditional in
Buddhism, be for you, store, or before
you study anything, busts, team,
the teacher must do the falling work
about emptiness,
especially the female, you'll see for yourself, just that  At
the end, you can see 500 years into the future.
What will you do in 500 years?
You can see.
Each person intends to achieve
minutes and you can have direct love for
each of the living. There are
7 billion living beings and
Q&A queues. Ask him. He ate the walls in 20
minutes and this is called.
At first, you Rima, a gimmick, a
teacher's job. He sat there selling. He
works with the new one. You study this
Lam Rim.
You want to be in the future. You will become a Buddha
very soon. He gave children's work.
First, tell people what's
cool. D. B. G. Then they'll
get hungry. Sometimes people will say, "Now
teach or teach." Why did I tell you all this?
We break and day job of. And
Philip, my job teaching you Rima is
half finished. I still have five or six
years left. David J. And then it's your job in the
computer. New. Continue the next generation. The
only thing is, I don't need to dance
today. I already danced. I give it to the
next generation. I would say, "Well, I
understand Europe well." Demix, so you need to continue the next generation
before you teach.
So before that.  How do you teach
people like you? You need to explain why
it's cool if you learn to meditate. This is
business. Sit
closer so you can hear me. We're making a
business program and meditation. They say
I don't want to learn to change like in
Russia without burra.
I'm not a Buddhist.
I want to. Why do
I really need to learn meditation? Why do I need to
learn meditation? If a business person
studies meditation, good meditation. Yes, and
can see what's this new water. Defer. They
can see a product from next years this
year. They can see the iPhone
next years this year. This moment. If
they are on the sales market, whether it's a q object,
they can see when the stock will go up.
Probably, therefore, you need to do
sales work. A businessman
for businessmen. And you want to meditate.
Well, for years, she's been storming and a won't be. I'll b d l d t yes, well, you
see, with the left they can. If you
meditate every day, you
can see which stocks will go up
next year. I think I like it. You need to
sell. You need to sell.
Rome and meditation is a Buddhist tradition.
You, that is, a tourist began to
introduce a student into a state of delight.
Helium.  and so at first
regarding this path of agents one
guy rockfall companies owe a
lot of ideas when I come to your
programs these these these windows to
think I just want to use my
heart I don't need these 5 steps of
emptiness
or here comes just emptiness I just
want to use my heart and soul in
this tradition
you can at a ponder you cannot open your
heart without your mind
pathetic link in first comes understanding
pen need walls understanding pen without
understanding pen you cannot love you
cannot open your heart why as
power if your husband yells at you at home you
just get angry after you
study pen and became good before you
study lead you get angry at men
and then not if you can yell and became until after
you study who you are
angry at me understands you cannot
truly love maybe without you
cannot understand another person to love
that person if you do not recognize the seeds
in this tradition
you cannot love maybe fidan one
if you do not understand who made him
good VAT in this tradition you and I we
think about opening the heart you can
really open your heart
if you understand it as a pen and  If
you think you can be an evil person, you will
never have a perfect marriage. This is
impossible. There will be a whole horde of you. This means
reaching an agreement for a while. It's not a
salty stand for you. If you don't understand
who did it, it's impossible to have a
wonderful, beautiful marriage.
This goal is an ironclad marriage. It's the most
magnificent thing in this world. But it's
impossible. It's impossible if you don't
understand where your husband is coming from. A
woman came up to me and said, "I
need help." I'm married to my husband. A
38-year-old Chinese woman is initially a shareholder,
and a Chinese woman should cook. I
understand this. I'm not complaining.
I like to cook for my family. I
can take on this responsibility.
Dance, but under the interest of forum cookies.
For 30 years, I've been cooking for my husband and may
never have washed the dishes even once.
Sylvester looks stressed about the content. If there's
some way I can change it
using the seed system, he said, "
Drive in 3 steps." Then, first, you need
to see what you want. I want your husband to do
the dishes. Then, find a karmic
partner. Then, I need to find a chock
who has too much work to think about,
movies, lots of coffee, meditation.  Wards USB
I told four steps I'm returning to the
country and come to my place for dinner in the center
here I have something to show them
but I came I'll give you a land mine and she has a
beautiful house drive away Rebecca Blizzard I won't
say which city because
you'll guess the window and there's a big
table it's her burning sit above him on the
table there's nothing but a small
bell here's something else
I want to show you this gives
the bell tower the door to the canal opens and
he can go in about m n o p he has
women's ports dislike and he's like that there's
dinner ready legs not finished yet he's walking
in the kitchen this happened in the fall whales you
hope I told about how to
wash dishes I don't know it took just 2
months
18 times I did four steps 58 thousand and he
started washing dishes screws and I think at Ivy
buy stop here why do I need to
stop here one because of the false
start Lego how can I also
use four steps so that he year I
did this mountains in the compartment and he now
Cooks,
but there are no arguments in the file, dota, in the cafe,
no discussions. She didn't even ask
him to cook food for love. She didn't
ask him to wash the dishes. A son,
because he comes from her seeds,
should follow your
son. You see, I can say, you just
need love.
Go home, let you have love, and
tell your husband,
I love bodies. You can't, please. Sometimes
we're like,
and then a big war will start. Catch
indexes. Cyston. In the seed system. You can do it with your
hands. It happens through honor.
Hill, strong. Here, you'll change. Think, and the
husband will change. While he had darkness, and so it is for
me at night, but Jan Fried and the
display activities after this class. I have
this special, special class. Life. Resentment.
Eraser. 500 dollars to come,
and banking. Only a man for men.
How to play. Style. How to plant a seed.
Tyumen. Abo.ua. States. Part. Never. So as
not to wash dishes.
Rubles. Well
[applause].
And water. Years. And if you want to go deeper, reach
us. Codes.
Let's go deeper. Feel.
Watched the movie Titanic.
I'm there. The biggest
chips. I think.  It was the
largest ship in the world, or 80, and it was
new, so the first time you use it, any. Here's the
first time you used it,
sister, homosexuals, and here comes the Titanic, an
iceberg mountain bike.
If a ship collides with an iceberg,
we try a big problem. Destin, you understand,
yes, and from the PC and became live sets in Urma,
asberg
is the seeds of wives with parts, histamine, we
sit and Zman, and Titanic
is the seeds, we can get it from has been
hamsters,
this iceberg is the seeds, we can get it with crowbars,
the ship
is strong, women wash dishes,
who will win, sponsor seeds, can
grains of numbers, strong, well, it's not particularly
possible, you don't have any, but no one will
wash dishes.
Khabib
can't be that both are
right, this is especially embarrassing, the Turks are
impossible, so he may not be able to, there's
no point in washing dishes with our hands,
and we should already be hiring, someone
must be the dishes on Sunday itself, so
that she, the facade, humanists will give Ubby a map
of one, Montserrat, so much a woman
or a man must be stronger, and guests,
you understand, by can both can food,
both can be  Right, indak, this adapter
in the kitchen, maybe
my wife is capable of
giving in to the wife's kitchen, you can wash dishes
from Isha, the teacher was killed. Notice how there
can be two kitchens in one kitchen, and
holes, you understand
well, you understand how the Bible
can be a pen, maybe a
chew toy. I'll clean it. We
finished the first index with there in this
system, it ate, but true love is
industry.
I understand. I love my work. I
improve my own. Maybe it's good when we
reset things here, and maybe I can also
improve my wife, and then harmony in the kitchen.
You can't have love for a long time. The whole
understanding of emptiness. He needs to think about
indices. So, on this path, it is said, but
this training is the path from this first step.
Dance. You need to study the instructions.
I disappear in spirit. This is our tradition. If you
teach things, if they have already done it in
class, use this position. This will be
Buddhism. This is our tradition.
First, study the news
and then use the house. Shares. Give
my sales team.
This is my sales job and Mars in my
house. My Monaco partner, Veronica,
chemistry, B8000.
She never washes dishes. I say.
Let's morph, how I cut my finger,
I cook like this, and they measure the
smokiness, you,
I made a big mistake, foreign currency, my
class, I invited my class, 2, I draw resin,
May there's a small green light,
give me light
[music],
all the food in the world, bring it to the mayor's office, but there are
many things that young people should know,
debates, for example, you studied the pen, there it is, it
goes, and I still don't need
your pens, you have another one, there are
two more, she wants to
advertise pens
before you came to my training, you
thought it was just a pen, didn't give 2 ha
bars, and you didn't think about it until you were at the computer, does
it happen or does it come from the
pen, here someone else will ask, but
where does it come from, from the pen or from
you, tell me, I don't care, 1 for just
have fingers, munin gray, but in shape, a pen
from me, you don't, then you custom, if you
figure out where the pen comes from, your
husband will wash dishes forever, about
painful, tell on the pen,
thereby the third bathub, and then someone
will tell you about the pen before you  Somewhere
before they teach you, the handles here
from the wings to cmis, it's like darkness,
where this handle comes from, and a person for 3
months,
since the darkness itself, and then someone
teaches you dogs and hands, New Line
Cinema, and a new light occurs in your
consciousness, so Andy,
billions of voids in the world, I'll finish off the intensive, Don,
billions of things that you don't know, 1 for
us, but now one of them
becomes light,
and we saw at the beginning,
10 in the background, so down for you, this is darkness,
but I'm flying out, Balditsyn, by school, no one would have
told you about this.  Instas your
parents - along and then you came and
so not joints like and this darkness became
light if you can high line
if you come to Thailand Thailand
pain pain in any pain highline
come on is the new every time a
new light arrives and a new light in
the head the release date is what we do up
to 100 billion speed
this is the meaning of this picture okay then
I don't tell these people
1x printer mother next drawing from 100
dollars
sabre well a little
to ribbons
someone teachers don't answer this
drawing are called outs absolutely at
least portable
wealth in Kol explain to me gave herself
who can explain this to me 100 dollars
and Gaidamakov he excuse me here and
[music]
you give me
I can do business
by the way I need two things in return and two
parts and you balayan happy up to 50 dollars and
50 dollars then repeat the question
will file a lawsuit this drawing is called
absolute at least portable
portable reassign what you can
take with yourself little  There will be little clarity;
you can choose a chair from the pressure; it
was sent not portable, not
portable,
shock, and to eat with your ears.  Eve,
this is if the answer is Sasha, the length of the usual is
wrong
[music]
what was said earlier,
you need to put money in people's banks
to return there and through this is a
good answer, but not to this question,
someone else on YouTube, how to choose, choose
then they won't choose with me
sometimes, of course, behind Germany,
any student, part 2 of the answer,
part 1 comes from us moment by
moment, and the second part is 4, we're naughty, you
can be a decent one, you can be 10, a
thought giver, receive this is the answer, 10 g
or Kostenyuk, one any question, I'll take
you, I think you need from the breeds, I rarely
went out and so Germany, dupe, scream
[music] a
collection of
merits and wisdom, and one more of 9
festina,
we need, today, Ukraine graduated,
Olfein, good evening, pressure, what will you
answer in the lesson, I hope you answer well, we
think that you, the first answer is that there is
emptiness in everyone, in every thing, and the
second is that you can share
this knowledge with anyone, it's like
absolute
wealth, evil in your pocket, you don't
need anything to share, this is
those wisdoms are milked this is the beginning of the answer
[music]
[music] they
pay off the debt I'll tell you a joke from the place
lynch and boot knife and cathedral that I
went to a restaurant downgrade with a friend a
few days ago he 5 model BATE, moreover,
one bathroom at
one end and this and a large
space men de parfum des men's
bath there will be three without women's on
there odometer sleep and below the signature
men have to go there on men must
go left why broken
because a woman is always right because of
you he and cream
Grigoryants therefore his wife gave a
good enough woman on the shortcomings
here and the whole set 1 watch online in disk
class is here you can why you
study in this class there will always be
you here you can choose anywhere
and 1 darkness
if tomorrow war starts peace wolf you
know world war people and you lose
your home you can't go back home you can't
return home you stand you will
need to stay in Thailand for the rest of
your life but puts and you will lose
everything south and with your cars a house is like a
bank account than his  U10 index class
you can do windows on what you study
in this class you will never lose
now I'm kind of no one will take it away from you,
he also has experience and it's insured and
property you skates with you can
save,
but the information didn't confuse skates and Pierre and
study things you can
save real m bank account can
break
composite maybe something is wrong anything is it
possible can you lose
your hand
Albe new computer whether on these ideas no
one will take you from you they always
tried safe Annie Besant moments the
second part of the answer
stage full then you can track with you
you are not yes this is the only thing
you can free when you can't
take the body with the economy you can't
take the family cannot be with you
and you can't even take your name from
Isolde, but these ideas alms
they will remain in your mind and TVEL
is to give to a lady precious as a diamond
bridge and the most portable, etc.  It's worth it
if the whole world collapses, you can do this
solitude
and how if you die, you can take it with you,
cool, that's a good answer
[applause]
if you have roses at the exit, you want to
give them so I can bless you, after the
program, you can
bring this every day, camera 2, we'll arrive,
rosary beads, ok,
I'm frickin' changing, we have another 15 minutes, that's the next one, the
next performance is already
ready, the next one, everything, the whole picture, 112
UAH and Matyukha and the end of March and we're going to
Astana, I think Shakespeare or the game The
Country can be beaten on Joomla like
Germany,
land of agony, you have any sex with
one guy wanted to buy success, whether
something holding and books, your
one powerful being said I
can of this round,
but I
need I think it's from Excel, I thought so,
it's magic, I can get success for this
for the rest of my life and I won't take away the empty one, there's a
beautiful thing that I became, then I myself became
soft as a few people,
he loved to kill people and eats and lives, he
comes out of there, they kidnap people and
eats and  People found out, didn't know it
was two thousand years ago. If they see
him, everyone ran,
she was very strong, and there was a prince who
had very often hearts, foundations, and one day he
became able to go to the registry office, came for his
throat with people in the courtyard,
and he was going to take 2-3 people, you drink,
and a handsome prince with a pure heart, feel
like the story himself, glam, and he studied lam
rim, and to the palace, and he kidnapped 2-3
who else, dolfer, and the prince came to him
without fear,
everyone else and principles, and ask them
if you need to eat someone, time
without NSM battle, Barbie house,
they are innocent people, not needed, it happens, you
look quite fundamentally like that, and
then he took from the sites and began to make
fire to Tynda, in principle, such, and the prince
began to cry,
good forward dance and a
soldier of the device after de de de de de de de de de de to
be the prince of this country,
usapl individuals bff, you must be a man, here
you sit, look, either the prince
says what are you talking about and Ukraine you
You pay with a hole, yes, I pay, that's why
you ask him to the company,
you're afraid of me, I have him, why do you
pay YouTube and in a form we break rights, you
took me from my lam rim class,
frequent
of the entire video, I now have no
chance to make a relationship with the teacher
[music]
now I had no chance to
thank my teacher, I want to
thank
about water and the principle of the view, I have an idea,
prince, and I'm a prince, said the
hand of a monster
[music]
megafaun is coming,
give me, I'll return to the palace, I must
thank my teacher to make a
relationship, this is this file, lines, and I delayed
with this, he taught me only four
opinions, tribute, 1st, you came, I want you to
come, I want to come thank
the teachers again,
and then I'll return, maybe we have something
called and caught, and he says and thinks
I'm a stupid monster and you won't
return as a wolf.
and the princess got angry, I'm running away. So you think
I'm like that, he's like that, and I have honor, but at
home I respect you, I'm not like
Kim, my I kept my word, kill and
bible, and Rome, people,
you kill people, and Charleville, I'm not like
you, Akimova,
I keep my word, Dynamo was demolished,
I'm ashamed, or daddy, Ufa, debts, and the
monster said yesterday where your father went,
he drove out on the wrong side, why was I swimming in the photo,
subtil, you know, about this, father also kills,
yes, that's good, you knew it, me,
you're a prince and a king, I'm the same as me, the
press is such a know-it-all, but no, you're worse,
why do you eat people, this is yours, it's worse, and the
monster says, the Ministry of Emergency Situations, and so I'm interested to
see, will you return, years old, and Adyghe, like a wolf, I
think you won't return, Google,
and at the road accident, running, you have an idea, I made an
idea for a self-study guide, thanks to the teacher,
and say goodbye, and I was only banks, and
let's see if you come back, they gave me,
and the faithful prince, Besbaev, M.S., this is very
Known for his happy ending of each
online, he paid a thousand gold coins
for each figure with ideas like Sasha's, while
he paid 1,000 gold coins
for each line, these and the United League of Pindos, he gave a thousand pieces. They beckon.
He said, "Teacher, I need to go. I
won't come back. I love you. I hope for the
next life. I promised to come back and
add to the barbecue." Crazy,
you don't have to keep your word.
This is going to be. Throw it over your head, than
some kind of box. The role will be bad. The
Poles are not from Batman. The king must be
dark, and well, without leaving a rake about you
in stages, and the sign "Got You Continue." The
king must make promises, but if
the promises are not good, he must change
Okunev's promise on the computer, and he's cheerful.
How can you rule the country if it's the same as
predicted. This is a bad
king. A good king keeps his word.
An event with a monster. Even a monster. The king
will keep his word. And he returned. And the
monster, who returned? I promised. I
kept my word. I'm ready.
Prepare for the bridges of Govinda. And the monster
got angry.
This is my...  I decided when to eat, but
Isaeva's YouTube hands, I'll decide for myself
when to cook you, just wait, gives
what they taught you there, wanted to return,
what they taught you, it's
burning, well, they told me the peculiarities,
can you teach me about deming
and the meaning of glass?
If you have you, even if it costs you, you
need to cut
online, pay
a hundred thousand for one line. The test is
more expensive, it's stylish, and such
was the monster's clothes around his chest, put it
on a stone, did the prince's rubbing, and I
teach children to be. You're a good teacher, and he
began studying the drama. You're a monster, a monster, and
then he saw emptiness
on the straight edge. Cool story. Edit
for his love, which means that this is the exact thing.
Rakovich, even if you are stupid, aromas of
entry, fingering, even if you need to
grab a lot of money for a ticket to
Hawaii, no work,
it's worth it, and spider UMV,
there are people who cut off their hand, the same
shape, 17 years old, and Tate killed at the junction
in order to gain this knowledge. The
wind in out, you have us, and three hours on a
plane,
14 hours at customs,
and  One train to get from here isn't that
bad I don't know three hours just okay yeah
Bauer One 1 113k purely in the picture the
dog is showing off she's about the relationship
between student and teacher idol and during the
monster Landrin tradition it's like
artificial respect Turin students
hair villages they all worship
they say don't touch the choice we bring in
Komi
all the herbs I served my teacher for 30 years
dishwasher
I did laundry everyone you saw hundreds these
roads suit
you I'll show respect they all force no
one loves them looked for time these
types these stages batik this is my teacher
and you will stand aside without touching him in
history so blow what do you think you're
making an album or less sometimes mister and
I have seen very many such
students relies on however I have seen
others others lacquer lama come in they are
like you want can you make beautiful ty
thank you for the starting teaches you such and
cool her classes for
you such cool classes make wines
my mom is from Tibet and it feels like
lamas and  I love female students, good ones, we have
affection in English, and the same thing as
respect. Respect is something like this, an
artificial llama. The llama goes
dimmer in Africa,
but this affection made
me so happy. I somehow didn't
tell you how
powerful the handles are, the new one is better, and Pillay Civic. Yes, you're so
pressurized, and the dog is another thing.
Find it. Video from the bureau.
Imagine your teacher. Travelers,
where do they go in Thailand? Compare 50
bureaus. Respect. As if there
are two types of respect. You suspect San
Martino.
One is respect from the mouth. Words. Everyone is
happy. Respect. Jigme. About 7
personal walls. 25 years. We have
respect for our true selves.
I don't love you, not a cat. Ladronka.
We need you to live long and teach.
You must respect. I love you. I want you to
stay.
Jackal. Feel this affection. This
kind of people is better. Respect is the highest
love,
and it appeals to us. How did I
come here? Try to look like a
real student. Rima is a gift. I
love you. I like this monster on ours. It
seems to me that I am porcelain, and 44 of
yours.  Students must fill out your pit
mn.ru sometimes bio bio
but it will be the entire monastery of the
subsequent teacher, therefore, or repent,
our line for a deuce is
not too cold, we ride the line
that gets to the site inside like a
female leg, maybe s shop with sharp Pirelli
behavior,
you understand, this is your family now Ubykhs,
our family tradition altanza not
millennia,
this is friendly joyfully tire Jane
dancing time Dorman shob was
strict correct and all things 2000 books
sank sharply on feelings like a dog
is real respect,
real respect is affection,
let's take another picture of Gella
Chara
and then we will have a question about your
main one this is the last half hour, after all, you
and they are poor excuse if you want to go to the
toilet, go if you want just
settlers 1 answers
but my job is to finish one more three
cups Steve is ready raises his hand the very
first teacher of course side microphone
reach the goal come on in tourism clearly will
say Buddhism
tour good students should not be like
three cups were clearly the
first you cannot mix teachings this is the
first you cannot  mix the teachings
second you must be open to learning
not to turn it over not to distort and there
should be no crack in the cup in the
warm pile and quieter.  Crowd, quiet down, you
tiger, give me a loud bang, I left the show, fifth, a little
silence, anti, here's some
gelatin for you, and he died, a little crowded, you'll
get there yourself, and the panel, along the way, I'm more often guessing, I'm
writing
somewhere, warm pita bread, Chopin, like
bars
[applause],
question and answer, then you're a sex movie, and he didn't
finish today, 66 overviews, an apartment with
past arthritis, and we have a corrupt
salesman, you're in the light, we have
portable wealth, benefit, event, to the USB
port, and even if you cut off your skin, it's
worth it, your flesh.  This one in Africa
we have a binding they took care of we
have three cups from Steve with me and tomorrow
evening we should know all this better I'll
check
but the strange one I'll choose the name yoga is a
microphone take the microphone moments to
report is wrong like this will be
good questions you my battle would if you
need an example official at fibo
and once for tea drinks
if you want to go home very
quietly secret organ please
welcome to leave artin now question
answer and time on this I have 20
minutes left
good morning I was just walking
thank you very much for coming to
teach us I have a question about
death
[music]
if
if the person in front of me I see
you and
[music]
and it's very difficult for me to breathe two things
that arise in my consciousness
first
tell the person to calm down and breathing
through the process of death is the first second I
always remind the person
what good things he or she did
when they were alive besides these two
things what can I do for a person
when his things are difficult to breathe
[music]
maybe this person in a couple of hours
he or she is already completely  will leave how can I
help this person
when this person has never
attended any
trainings so that he understands emptiness and I don’t
know the answer to this
[applause] which one are
you coming from I’m from
.
good question, I asked the self-study guide
about this data and this means our
line,
so when you become teachers, you can
say, I'm Sasha, location in line, this is the
transfer of generations, in my case, my
father was a very large man
and he really liked to take care of and he
killed a lot of animals, let him
even have a boat for a fisherman, well, just
for fun, for fun,
he took us fishing in the ocean
[music]
small, it was 7 years old and he taught us
how to fish and also once killed a
deer, he taught us this available to
us and taught how to clean the killed
animal and fish, especially this is possible, we
go to the article and you start from the bottom
and you go up like this,
first, then open the body of the
animal and these are its insides,
naturally, don't go, you
take it all out oak, and with a deer,
when this starts, the woodpecker's
flights are completely
covered in blood because blood
splashes and the first time it doesn't affect the matzo,
I can't do this anymore and he
tries very hard and we grew up in
Arizona is such a cowboy zone and this is our
tradition to live like this all the young people
killed deer caught fish behind him he got
very angry and his doctor said
your father needs a special operation and
what kind of operation should be delighted hammer from here we will
start and we
cut Putin up and I
just saw
surprised we will take the leg here and
put it
and I didn't know then feed nothing but I
thought this patronymic is definitely the same as how
the mayor cut the fish and how we
cut the deer and then this
really later when my father
got cancer I studied Buddhism already then
I asked the teacher my father was
dying they opened him up cut him up and
looked in and if everything is forgotten
joy and for sewn up we can't help
and I'm in his last in the last
few weeks and I asked my father
a question then what can I do then what
can I help my father from magic and
as you just said
1 before inventing there is a very good
Christian tradition to steal from
some listening when Chuck dies out yu
k and you  You call the priest, he comes from
the eyes and he generally asks everyone to
leave and this person
leaving is left alone with the priest
and the priest asks the citizens will be completely
bad at the beginning you want
to talk
and storms plan and here we are exactly the
same if you did something bad made a
mistake
if you tell someone about it, it
will help you cleanse this seed will
help a lot, it helps a lot
review if you say sorry here dougi
I will not do this again this is
definitely destroying and then we teacher
told me your with
your father fast and the first thing
see if you can ask him
what bad was done life doping and 2
as you said remind him of the good things
who took his life and Yaga Baba you
told me to always respect other people a
good businessman you told me and to be
honest with other people
you taught me work a lot thank
you for this I actually communicate very well
with children we have four brothers and I
said he never
thanked me these two things
first tell me if you want to
cleanse something realize you should play
with him like that me  Father, he's a man, he'll tie a
rope around his neck, he didn't like it. In
Omsk,
I stood there, I had to somehow do this
ceremony,
what doesn't need to be done? He can't
even eat anymore, he looked very much like he was just
watching TV, and I sat down next to him.
Watch TV. He was looking for Dad. I remember
you once had peas. You were in the war. You
said that you killed many people, and you
killed them. Will you do this? It's not so
bad. I gave him this one
as a catalyst. The hall so that he would clean out
this seed. You can say that by chance, you can do it like that.
You don't need to say
that this is some kind of religious
thing. Just provoke them to
tell you that they didn't do this, and
so that they say that they won't, and the
lever, and this seed immediately ends. The
last piece of advice: if a person dies
within 49 days of mass battle, it's
possible that they come across Barton,
something about Kabardino, for no reason. This is a blessing for
these people, for eBay, for a baby.
But in general, don't forget that they are
comfortable on the computer, have a drink, and they come to the
kitchen, and everyone looks around, doesn't understand
why everyone  color .
but no one can hear them and they
say the same old thing in this guy's number
because all thoughts are about a tomato but they do
n't see him anymore and he gets very upset and
my family is my currency what ignore me
I'm actually asking you a question and people
ignore them for the first hours after that people get
very upset and then they
suddenly begin to understand that they have already
died this border of his so they can
be in this state for 49
days maybe they want to be in the house
of course they listen to what you say the
move is very cool to say good
things that we get during our
life and the old my dots said that the
park for the time of Bordeaux is a lottery in
when I will of life we ​​talk about that and in
the wheel of life sundae these are parts 890 or
a little doctor you at that moment
choose the seeds that you will be
which will close the next
life and words
and I asked the teacher I saw this knows
what this means and this is actually an
advantage to stay closer to
the night of the maiden bell he lived upstairs you just
need to actually they even were
studying the
event but my lamo liked watching
the news play
and was preparing that  The bell rang, I
quickly ran to the world of business, for me
it meant something important, I ran,
look, the answer to the question, what's the question, the hell,
I care what this
special word "jen" means, and segmentation by death,
he look, look, there's a blizzard on TV,
and every evening in America, at the
same time, at 7 p.m., there's
something special for you, for our buns, a
beautiful woman in a very short skirt,
windows look out on the TV screen, and
they have a special wheel there, stop,
and she stops it, there, inside, her
hand, he chickened out, and pulls out some kind of tray
for the whole country, about 20 million
people play this lottery, and everyone waits, and
when you get their number, and it's mine, and take into account this, there's a
printer, during
death in Bordeaux, this person pulls out
this lottery number, a lot of
good things have been done, and also not so much,
and you have 1000 seeds,
but one seed will allow that you will still have
life, this is a very, very important point, and
this seed lasts about 70-80
years, will you be an
animal, will you be a human, and
your slave lasted  Big nose or small
nose, American nose, Chinese nose, noise, I
drink it, it will be your decision, but this is a very
important point. This is very important before
the,
before they die, rock, years of experience,
talk about the name of those good things
they did in their reserves, the governor,
never never fight, don't swear, who
takes money from someone, big
I am what am I on the list or not when
never swear at the person who
leaves, drank everything should be calm,
everything should be happy, just
talk to them about the good things
they did in their life after
they die, they listen to you, they
watch you, that one talk with your
family, dare
you remember dad, such good things
he made a choice,
he helped everyone in 1515, he helped a
poor family, an angel, he gave them new
iPhones,
he was a very good father, headlights, and dad
will be like that with you, so avi, yes, that's for
sure, I remember on a small set of
commands, deception, and
if at that moment this lottery
number pops up on YouTube, you helped
him have a better life option, rubles, it
hurts, it's very important, the first seven bullets are
49 days, and the first day is the day of the media,
start with vegetables if they die
it will be the first day from this day very
carefully in the house where they taught to fight
together with your family very carefully
talk only about good things this
section because it will serve you
maybe it will work will it trailer
very good year ticket all the last
questions we are going to sleep the USA and at home jigme
suddenly a woman
I am her daughter died 20 years ago 20 years
ago her daughter died and at that moment this
girl was only 20 we will pass otherwise
young she left this woman came to
me you are standing she was absolutely me life
was times
when parents die it is very hard
when a child in the family dies before a
parent this is the most probably terrible it
could be she was so simply
destroyed and depressed and began to
speak more clearly turnover please says
within the next 7 weeks good
cheerful daughter
good things and I recently saw her I
told her that 20 years have already passed oh yes
I still talk to
my daughter every my coffee meditation
I talk to her it is so beautiful
we have such a wonderful relationship I am very
happy I am very happy I feel
happy you know you don't even have to
stay  After 7 weeks,
continue doing this for the rest of your
life. This is one of the reasons to become
Buddhas forever. Family loves to
travel and be together again. Death is a
temporary period.
Separation is temporary, it is not permanent. This is
one of the reasons for studying emptiness.
To meet them again, let's lose with
them again. Let's
downsize. The house,
so don't worry. Just
talk to them and never,
never scold your relatives
when they leave. Just
talk about something good with them. The club is cool.
Now it will be
[music].
Come on,
Bogdanov's day.
Sochi. Don't shake it.
And
this is also the creation of
Vlad
and Tonkino.
They have something else. He
can do it.
Like,
I
love him.
[music].
Seeker,
what are we doing anyway.
[music].